[{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664245167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":37319,"timeElapsed":121677},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664264451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":19283,"timeElapsed":140961},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664293928,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":29475,"timeElapsed":170438},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664304793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":10863,"timeElapsed":181302},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664316619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":11825,"timeElapsed":193129},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664323183,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":6562,"timeElapsed":199692},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664330435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":7251,"timeElapsed":206945},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664338730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":8292,"timeElapsed":215239},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664342874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4142,"timeElapsed":219384},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664371122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":25365,"timeElapsed":247632},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664381231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":10107,"timeElapsed":257741},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664389667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":8435,"timeElapsed":266177},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664395829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":6160,"timeElapsed":272339},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664401717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":5887,"timeElapsed":278227},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664405350,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3631,"timeElapsed":281860},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664422230,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":16879,"timeElapsed":298740},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664426319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4087,"timeElapsed":302829},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664430868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"139","question":"What is a good number of people to have in a family or household and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4548,"timeElapsed":307378},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664446840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":13546,"timeElapsed":323350},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664450197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3356,"timeElapsed":326707},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664454917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":4718,"timeElapsed":331427},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664459516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":4598,"timeElapsed":336026},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664462713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3195,"timeElapsed":339223},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664466530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3816,"timeElapsed":343040},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664469686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3154,"timeElapsed":346196},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664474906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":5218,"timeElapsed":351416},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664478654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3746,"timeElapsed":355164},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664491787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":11278,"timeElapsed":368297},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664516291,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":24503,"timeElapsed":392801},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664525295,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9002,"timeElapsed":401805},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664530354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":5058,"timeElapsed":406864},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664535384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":5028,"timeElapsed":411894},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664538539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3154,"timeElapsed":415049},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664543158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":4617,"timeElapsed":419668},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664546574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":3415,"timeElapsed":423084},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664549760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3184,"timeElapsed":426269},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664552955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3194,"timeElapsed":429465},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664573165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":18425,"timeElapsed":449675},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664576311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3145,"timeElapsed":452821},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664583425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":7112,"timeElapsed":459935},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664589717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":6290,"timeElapsed":466227},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664594396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":4678,"timeElapsed":470906},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664598362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3965,"timeElapsed":474872},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664613667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":15303,"timeElapsed":490177},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664617434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":3766,"timeElapsed":493944},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664621332,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3896,"timeElapsed":497842},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664640713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":17596,"timeElapsed":517223},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664647662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":6948,"timeElapsed":524172},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664652318,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":4655,"timeElapsed":528828},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664659522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":7202,"timeElapsed":536032},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664663639,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":4116,"timeElapsed":540149},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664666735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3094,"timeElapsed":543245},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664670171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":3435,"timeElapsed":546681},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664674499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":4326,"timeElapsed":551009},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664677274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2773,"timeElapsed":553784},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664710028,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":30789,"timeElapsed":586538},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664713955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3926,"timeElapsed":590465},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664717902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3946,"timeElapsed":594412},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664720998,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3094,"timeElapsed":597508},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664725115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4116,"timeElapsed":601625},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664729703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4586,"timeElapsed":606213},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664740092,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10388,"timeElapsed":616602},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664746112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6019,"timeElapsed":622622},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664752379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":6266,"timeElapsed":628889},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664758308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5927,"timeElapsed":634818},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664774021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":9476,"timeElapsed":650531},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664776496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2473,"timeElapsed":653006},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664780132,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3635,"timeElapsed":656642},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664782576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2443,"timeElapsed":659086},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664785391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2813,"timeElapsed":661901},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664788346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2954,"timeElapsed":664856},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664792423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4075,"timeElapsed":668933},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664800056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":7631,"timeElapsed":676566},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664803842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3785,"timeElapsed":680352},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664812591,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5922,"timeElapsed":689101},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664815726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3134,"timeElapsed":692236},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664818601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2873,"timeElapsed":695111},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664823039,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4436,"timeElapsed":699548},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664826284,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3244,"timeElapsed":702794},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664829569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3284,"timeElapsed":706079},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664834427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4856,"timeElapsed":710937},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664838223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3795,"timeElapsed":714733},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664843131,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"39","question":"What kind of activities help you recharge?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":4906,"timeElapsed":719641},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664852756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":7860,"timeElapsed":729266},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664856482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3724,"timeElapsed":732992},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664859667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3184,"timeElapsed":736177},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664863423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3755,"timeElapsed":739933},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664866558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3134,"timeElapsed":743068},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664869974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3414,"timeElapsed":746484},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664879229,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":9254,"timeElapsed":755739},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664884658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5427,"timeElapsed":761168},{"subjectID":"e5h6gtg85c","prolificID":"67333b848e895456bb1d7f2b","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421daf59d62d8af7a4c90","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664888644,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"156","question":"What is the best TV show or movie that you have seen in the last month? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3985,"timeElapsed":765154}]